Your darkest dream awaits you.
The Ritual is a horror, mystery film directed by David Bruckner.
A group of college friends reunite for a trip to the forest, but
encounter a menacing presence in the woods that's stalking them.
Luke, played by Rafe Spall.
Phil, played by Arsher Ali.
Hutch, played by Robert James-Collier.
Dom, played by Sam Troughton.
Robert, played by Paul Reid.
Junkie, played by Matthew Needham.
The Ritual is a 2017 British supernatural psychological folk horror film
directed by David Bruckner and written by Joe Barton.
Based on the 2011 novel of the same name by Adam Nevill, the film stars Rafe Spall, Arsher Ali, Robert James-Collier, and Sam Troughton
as four friends on a hiking trip through a Swedish old-growth forest, where they encounter an ancient evil presence.
Following its world premiere at the 2017 Toronto International Film Festival on 8
September, The Ritual was released by eOne in the United Kingdom on 13 October.
The film explores themes of robbery, monster, based
on novel or book, nightmare, sweden.
The tone is dark and mind_bending.